ecvv.com 2010-01-11

# Privacy Policy | ecvv.com

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Ecvv.com,This is our policy to protect your own privacy. By using this site, you may be clear with how your personal information is used and the process of our work. This policy may change without notice, so please check back periodically. 

**A. Information**

a. Registration Information  
When you register as an ECVV.com member we collect all the information you enter. This includes your own name, company name,contact ways etc. Membership statistics are derived from members' registration information, however no specific member is named or referred to in the resultant statistical reports. Statistics are generally used to classify our members by, for example, industry and country. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested. 

b. Publishing Information  
We have the right to disclose your information when we think it's necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.   
We also have the rights to disclose, without notice to you, personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority.

c. Payment Information  
We think necessary thaat if you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from our site or a vendor available through ECVV, we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders.

**B.Cookies**

a. We may set and access cookies on your computer.   
We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to our cookies.   
We use web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with ECVV products and services.

b. Security Meastures  
All your information including account information and profile is protected.No data transmission over the Internet   
can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. however,we try our best to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

c. Attention  
We may change the information of it from time to time.If there is anything wrong or what you think have brought you some hurt,  
Please contact with us as soon as possible.

d. Feedback  
Welcome to leave your word.Or you can contact with us through CONTACT US.
